$onpcs_header_main_settings	Main OStim NPCs Settings
$onpcs_header_adjustments	Adjustments
$onpcs_header_reset	Reset Options
$onpcs_option_disable_onpcs	Disable automatic scene starts
$onpcs_option_allow_active_followers	Followers engage in scenes
$onpcs_option_allow_elders	Elder Race NPCs engage in scenes
$onpcs_option_allow_common_enemies	Enemies engage in scenes
$onpcs_option_stop_when_found	Scenes end when found
$onpcs_option_travel	Travel to location
$onpcs_option_travel_enemies	Enemies travel to location
$onpcs_option_enable_furniture	Enable furniture
$onpcs_option_furniture_beds	Furniture search - beds only
$onpcs_option_scenes_beds	Scenes start in
$onpcs_option_followers_dungeons	No follower scenes in dungeons
$onpcs_option_scenes_towns	No scenes in Towns
$onpcs_option_scenes_guilds	No scenes in Guilds
$onpcs_option_scenes_inns	No scenes in Inns
$onpcs_option_reset_defaults	Reset Defaults
$onpcs_option_add_spells	Add Matchmaking spells
$onpcs_option_remove_spells	Remove Matchmaking spells
$onpcs_option_min_relation	Minimum relationship
$onpcs_option_max_scenes	Max concurrent scenes
$onpcs_option_max_enemy_scenes	Max enemy scenes per night
$onpcs_option_min_night	Night start time
$onpcs_option_max_night	Night end time
$onpcs_option_scan_freq	Scan Frequency
$onpcs_option_scan_radius	Scan Radius
$onpcs_option_weight_mf	Male-Female scenes weight
$onpcs_option_weight_ff	Female-Female scenes weight
$onpcs_option_weight_mm	Male-Male scenes weight
$onpcs_message_box_option_yes	Yes
$onpcs_message_box_option_no	No
$onpcs_highlight_onpcs_disabled	Disable automatic scene start of NPCs and polling script. The match making spells are still possible to use.
$onpcs_highlight_allow_active_followers	Enable this if you want your followers to start scenes between them randomly.
$onpcs_highlight_allow_elders	Enable this if you want old people to engage in scenes started automatically by OStim NPCs.
$onpcs_highlight_allow_common_enemies	Enable this if you want enemies like bandits to engage in scenes between them randomly.
$onpcs_highlight_stop_found	NPCs will stop their scenes if they detect you.
$onpcs_highlight_travel	NPCs will travel to each other before starting the scene. If a furniture is found to start the scene on, they will travel to the furniture as well.
$onpcs_highlight_travel_enemies	Sets whether enemies will travel to each other before starting the scene or not. If a furniture is found to start the scene on, they will travel to the furniture as well.\nTurning this off might increase chances of finding enemies engaged in OStim scenes. However, there is also a small chance you might see enemies teleporting to each other to start OStim scenes.
$onpcs_highlight_enable_furniture	Sets whether NPCs will use furniture to start scenes on or not (they will only use furniture if there are valid furnitures available in their vicinity).
$onpcs_highlight_furniture_only_beds	Enable this if you want OStim NPCs to only search for beds if furniture is enabled. This option is good if you don't want NPCs starting scenes in chairs, benches or shelves, but want them to start scenes in no furniture at all or only in beds if there is furniture.
$onpcs_highlight_allow_scenes_in_beds	Set where you want scenes to start:\nAnywhere - NPCs will start scenes anywhere, whether there is furniture or not\nAny furniture - NPCs will only start scenes if any type of furniture is available\nBeds only - NPCs will only start scenes if beds are available
$onpcs_highlight_followers_dungeons	Enable this if you DON'T want followers to start scenes while you are adventuring in dungeons (this includes Nordic Tombs, mines, caves, keeps, etc).
$onpcs_highlight_scenes_towns	Enable this if you DON'T want scenes starting in the middle of the street in cities, towns, villages and settlements. Does not affect camps in the wilderness.
$onpcs_highlight_scenes_guilds	Enable this if you DON'T want scenes starting in guild halls, such as Jorrvaskr and the College of Winterhold.
$onpcs_highlight_scenes_inns	Enable this if you DON'T want scenes starting in Inns.
$onpcs_highlight_min_relation	Minimum relationship rank NPCs must have to start a scene. Relationship ranks are as follows:\n-4: Archnemesis | -3: Enemy | -2: Foe | -1: Rival\n0: Acquaintance | 1: Friend | 2: Confidant | 3: Ally | 4: Lover
$onpcs_highlight_max_scenes	The maximum number of NPC scenes that can run at the same time.
$onpcs_highlight_max_enemy_scenes	The maximum number of enemy scenes that can happen each night. This is for balance reasons for stealth characters. Check the mod page description for more info.
$onpcs_highlight_min_night	The time nights start at. NPCs will engage in OStim scenes starting from this hour. 8 PM is recommended.
$onpcs_highlight_max_night	The time nights end. NPCs will stop engaging in OStim scenes starting from this hour. 4 AM is recommended.
$onpcs_highlight_scan_freq	How often OStim NPCs scans for actors to start OStim scenes.
$onpcs_highlight_scan_radius	The radius from the player character from which actors are scanned.
$onpcs_highlight_weight_mf	How many of the scenes will be Male-Female.
$onpcs_highlight_weight_ff	How many of the scenes will be Female-Female. If you don't have lesbian animations installed, it's recommended to keep this at 0.
$onpcs_highlight_weight_mm	How many of the scenes will be Male-Male. If you don't have gay animations installed, it's recommended to keep this at 0.
$onpcs_message_defaults_reset	All options have been reset to their defaults.
$onpcs_message_spells_added	Matchmaking spells were successfully added.
$onpcs_message_spells_removed	Matchmaking spells were successfully removed.
